(Shopkeeper:)Can I help you?
(Sheldon:)Yes, according to information I gleaned
from Yelp...
(Sheldon:)...you had great success
when a SantariaSuzy37...
(Sheldon:)...brought you a pair of leather slacks
stained with chicken blood.
You know, I believe
I may have a similar problem.
(Sheldon:)This cushion experienced
a nude revenge wiggle.
(Shopkeeper:)A what?
(Sheldon:)A naked man sat on it.
(Sheldon:)Now, here's my concern.
(Sheldon:)His diet is rich in fatty deli meats.
What tests do you have
to detect lipid residue?
(Shopkeeper:)Lipid what?
(Sheldon:)Lipid residue.
(Sheldon:)An anal autograph.
(Sheldon:)A colon calling card, if you will.
- Tuesday okay?
- Oh.
(Sheldon:)Don't rush it. We may be dealing
with befoulment on a molecular level.
(Shopkeeper:)Let me write you a ticket.
(Sheldon:)Is that your son?
(Shopkeeper:)Uh-huh.
(Sheldon:)Looks like that laptop's seen better days.
(Sheldon:)If you're interested, I'm selling this.
It's only 2 years old...
...has 16 gigabytes of RAM...
(Sheldon:)...Intel Core i7 processor...
(Sheldon:)...and I can personally guarantee...
(Sheldon:)...it has spent less than 20 minutes
resting on an astronaut's penis.